Finding Aid for Clare E. Hoffman Papers 1934-1962
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Political files 1934-1962, 14.5 linear feet
  - 1953-1954
    - Advertisements
      - General Election (Box 63)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 63)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 63)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 63)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 63)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Campaign contributions (Box 63)
    - Campaign materials (Box 63)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 63)
    - Citizens for Eisenhower (Box 63)
    - Commendatory, 3 folders (Box 63)
    - Congratulations (Box 63)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Elections (Box 63)
    - Elferdink, Gordon A. (Box 63)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Fischer, Leslie H. (Box 63)
    - Fourth District Congressional Committee (Box 63)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Hicks, Hazel (Box 63)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 63)
    - Invitations (Box 63)
    - Kakebeeke, Lizzie (Box 63)
    - Killian, Joseph E. (Box 63)
    - Lamb, Rex (Box 63)
    - Loupee, Sherman L. (Box 63)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 63)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Patronage (Box 63)
    - Petitions, 7 folders (Box 63)
    - Publicity (Box 63)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 63)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 63)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 64)
    - Republican Policy (Box 64)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 64)
    - Republican organizations (Box 64)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 64)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 64)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Taft, Robert A. (Box 64)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 64)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
  - 1955-1956
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Adams, Dorothea (Box 64)
    - Adverse (Box 64)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 64)
      - General Election (Box 64)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 64)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 64)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 64)
    - Ball, Keith (Box 64)
    - Barry County Republican committee (Box 64)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 64)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Campaign contributions (Box 64)
    - Campaign materials (Box 64)
    - Campaign support (Box 64)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 64)
    - Colborn, I.L. (Box 64)
    - Commendatory, 3 folders (Box 64)
    - Congratulations (Box 64)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - District-County officials (Box 64)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Fischer, Leslie (Box 64)
    - Form letters (Box 64)
    - Fourth District Congressional Committee (Box 64)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Hicks, Hazel A. (Box 64)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 64)
    - Invitations (Box 64)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Kakebeeke, Lizzie (Box 64)
    - Lamb, Rex (Box 64)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Marvin, John W. (Box 64)
    - Material distribution (Box 64)
    - Michigan politics (Box 64)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 64)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 64)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - Petitions, 7 folders (Box 65)
    - Publicity (Box 65)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 65)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 65)
    - Republican Policy (Box 65)
    - Republican Publications (Box 65)
    - Republican State Central Committee (Box 65)
    - Republican State Convention (Box 65)
    - Republican organizations (Box 65)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 65)
    - Speakers (obtaining of) (Box 65)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 65)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - Taft, Robert A. (Box 65)
    - Union contributions (Box 65)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 65)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - Waterman, Maude (Box 65)
    - Young, Arthur M. (Box 65)
  - 1957-1958
    - Adams, Dorothea (Box 65)
    - Adams, Sherman (Box 65)
    - Advertisements
      - General Election (Box 65)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 65)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 65)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 65)
    - Bagwell, Paul D. (Box 65)
    - Ball, Keith (Box 65)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 65)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Brandt, Robert L. (Box 65)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 65)
    - Cain, Thomas W. (Box 65)
    - Campaign contributions (Box 65)
    - Campaign materials (Box 65)
    - Campaign support (Box 65)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 65)
    - Circular (Box 65)
    - Clark, Sam I. (Box 65)
    - Colborn, I.L. (Box 65)
    - Commendatory, 5 folders (Box 65)
    - Congratulations (Box 65)
    - Constituent comments (Box 65)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Daines, Luther (Box 66)
    - Democrats (Box 66)
    - District politics (Box 66)
    - Douthett, Dale I. (Box 66)
    - Duerr, Frank X. (Box 66)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Election returns (Box 66)
    - Elferdink, Gordon (Box 66)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Fischer, Les (Box 66)
    - Fourth District Congressional Committee (Box 66)
    - Harden, Edgar L. (Box 66)
    - Hicks, Hazel (Box 66)
    - Hoffman clippings (Box 66)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 66)
    - Hoffman voting record (Box 66)
    - Hutchinson, Edward (Box 66)
    - Invitations (Box 66)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Kakebeeke, Lizzie (Box 66)
    - Killian, Joseph E. (Box 66)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Lamb, Rex (Box 66)
    - Loupee, Sherman L. (Box 66)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Material distribution (Box 66)
    - Michigan politics (Box 66)
    - Michigan Republican policies (Box 66)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Nye, Harry (Box 66)
    - Osby, Charlotte (Box 66)
    - Petitions, 7 folders (Box 66)
    - Potter, Charles E. (Box 66)
    - Potts, J.F. (Box 66)
    - Press releases (Box 66)
    - Publicity, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Questionnaire (Box 66)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 66)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 66)
    - Republican Publications (Box 66)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Republican organizations (Box 66)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 66)
    - Songs - Poems
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 66)
    - Third Party (Box 66)
    - Union political contributions (Box 66)
    - Unions-Republican Party (Box 66)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 66)
    - Votes - In House (Box 66)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 66)
    - Winslow, Mary M. (Box 66)
  - 1959-1960
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Adams, Dorothea (Box 67)
    - Advertisements
      - Primary (Box 67)
      - General Election (Box 67)
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 67)
    - Americans for Constitutional Action (Box 67)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 67)
    - Bagwell, Paul D. (Box 67)
    - Ball, Keith (Box 67)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 67)
    - Bentley, Alvin M. (Box 67)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee, 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Burns, Edward (Box 67)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Cain, Thomas W. (Box 67)
    - Campaign contributions (Box 67)
    - Campaign support (Box 67)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 67)
    - Colborn, I.L. (Box 67)
    - Commendatory (Box 67)
    - Complaints (Box 67)
    - Congratulations (Box 67)
    - Constitutional Convention (Box 67)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Dames, Luther (Box 67)
    - Dean, Jack A. (Box 67)
    - Duerr, Frank X. (Box 67)
    - Election returns (Box 67)
    - Expense statements (Box 67)
    - Fourth District Congressional Committee (Box 67)
    - General election (Box 67)
    - Goldwater, Barry M. (Box 67)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Harrah, C.C. (Box 67)
    - Hoffman (candidate's file) (Box 67)
    - Hoffman speeches (Box 67)
    - Hoffman voting record (Box 67)
    - Hutchinson, Edward (Box 67)
    - Hutton, Nellie (Box 67)
    - Invitations (Box 67)
    - Irwin, Robert F. (Box 67)
    - Isham, Mary (Box 67)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Kakebeeke, Lizzie (Box 67)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - Material distribution (Box 67)
    - Michigan Republican Delegation (Box 67)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 67)
    - National Convention (Box 67)
    - Niles luncheon (Box 67)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 67)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - Petition letters (Box 68)
    - Petitions, 7 folders (Box 68)
    - Pomeroy, Paul (Box 68)
    - Presidential candidates (Box 68)
    - Publicity, 3 folders (Box 68)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - Republican accomplishments (Box 68)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 68)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 68)
    - Republican Policy (Box 68)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Republican miscellanea (Box 68)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - St. Joseph County Republican Committee (Box 68)
    - Shephard, Montgomery (Box 68)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 68)
    - State Convention (Box 68)
    - Summerfield, Arthur (Box 68)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - Van Buren County Republican Committee (Box 68)
    - Vice Presidential candidates (Box 68)
    - Voting (Box 68)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - White House (Box 68)
    - Williams, G. Mennen (Box 68)
    - Wright, Dotty, 2 folders (Box 68)
  - 1961-1962
    - Allegan County Republican Committee (Box 68)
    - Americans for Constitutional Action (Box 68)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 68)
    - Ball, Keith (Box 68)
    - Barry County Republican Committee (Box 68)
    - Berrien County Republican Committee (Box 68)
    - Berrien County Young Republican Federation (Box 68)
    - Boothby, Lee (Box 68)
    - Boyle, Robert E.A. (Box 68)
    - Burns, Edward (Box 68)
    - Byrns, Chester J. (Box 68)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - Campaign contributions (Box 68)
    - Cain, Thomas (Box 68)
    - Campaign support (Box 68)
    - Cass County Republican Committee (Box 68)
    - Colborn, I.L. (Box 68)
    - Complaints (Box 68)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - Dean, Jack (Box 68)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 68)
    - Harmon, Charles (Box 68)
    - Harrah, C.C. (Box 68)
    - Hoffman candidacy, 4 folders (Box 69)
    - Hutchinson, Edward (Box 69)
    - Invitations (Box 69)
    - Lamb, Rex E. (Box 69)
    - Miscellaneous requests (Box 69)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 69)
    - New Frontier (Box 69)
    - Pears, Don (Box 69)
    - Political organizations (Box 69)
    - Publications (Box 69)
    - Publicity (Box 69)
    - Reapportionment - Michigan (Box 69)
    - Republican Congressional Committee (Box 69)
    - Republican Joint Committee (Box 69)
    - Republican National Committee (Box 69)
    - Republican Publications (Box 69)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 2 folders (Box 69)
- Press Releases and Publicity 1939-1962, 2.5 linear feet
  The Press Releases series consists of four chronologically arranged subseries: Press releases, 1947-1962; Newsletters, 1939-1961; Form letters, 1951-1962; Radio releases, 1950-1961.
  - Press Releases
    - 1947-1957 (Box 69)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 70)
  - News letters
    - 1939-1961 (Box 70)
  - Form letters
    - 1951-1962 (Box 71)
  - Radio releases
    - 1950-1951 (Box 71)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 71)
    - 1957 (Box 71)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 71)
    - 1961 (Box 71)
- Sound Recordings
  Sound recordings of Clare E. Hoffman's radio-talks. There is no detailed listing of this portion of the collection
  [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1955 May 15, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; a political discussion about "Ideals" and corruption in the United States political system.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1956 February 10, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-2-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; A political discussion about the Gas Bill and campaign contributions.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1956 March 15, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-3-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 3; A political discussion of lobbying and the work of Senator John McClellan.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1956 March 23, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-4-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 4; a political discussion on foreign policies and treaties.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1956 April 12, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-5-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 5; About the death of six marines at Parris Island, South Carolina.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1956 April 12, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-6-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 6; About the death of six marines at Parris Island, South Carolina. Duplicate of 87140-SR-5. At 3:35 continues to a discussion of corn and wheat farming and the farm bill.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1956 May 02, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-7-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 7; Discussion of the death of six marines at Parris Island following the investigation.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1956 May 16, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-8-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 8; A political discussion on corruption in Washington.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1961 February 23, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-9-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 9; political discussion on the impeachment of Chief Justice Earl Warren, and the packing of the courts.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1961 August 24, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-10-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; Clare Hoffman discussing his skepticism on the moon program speculating that scientists are attempting to create a new race of humans to colonize outer space.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1961 September 27, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-11-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 11; A discussion centered around the weakening of the executive branch.)
  - Hoffman radio broadcast, 1961 September 27, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-12-1]; mp3 file; (Tape 12; A discussion centered around the weakening of the executive branch, duplicate of tape 87140-SR-11.)
  - Tape recordings taken by Lester Condon in Detroit: Track 1, William J. Patterson, Edward A. Grodzicki, 1953 April, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-13-1]; mp3 file; (Tapes relating to Detroit investigation by the Anti Racketeering Subcommittee 1953. Content is very quiet and difficult to hear.)
  - Tape recordings taken by Lester Condon in Detroit: Track 1, Walter Szewczyk; Track 2, Jay Coin, 1953 April, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-14-1]; mp3 file; (Tapes relating to Detroit investigation by the Anti Racketeering Subcommittee 1953.)
  - Tape recordings taken by Lester Condon in Detroit: Track 1, Henry C. Lemke; Track 2, Lemke Coun Machine Co., 1953 April 10, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-15-1]; mp3 file; (Tapes relating to Detroit investigation by the Anti Racketeering Subcommittee 1953.)
  - Tape recordings taken by Lester Condon in Detroit: Track 1, Ayres & Gold, 1953 April 09, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch
    - [Part 1], [87140-SR-16-1]; mp3 file; (Tapes relating to Detroit investigation by the Anti Racketeering Subcommittee 1953.)
  - Phono-records of talks, 5 phonograph records (Box 1)
    (not further described)
- Card indices 1937-1962, 8 linear feet
  The Card indices (8 card file boxes in 2 manuscript containers) series consists of indices (incomplete) to various series or subseries in the collection. Includes Hoffman House Talks, 1937-1947; Hoffman Bills, 1939-1962; Subject Index, 1943-1962; Bill Number Index, 1948-1962
  - Hoffman House Talks 1937-1947, 3 boxes (Box 72)
  - Hoffman Bills 1939-1962, 1 boxes (Box 72)
  - Subject Index 1943-1962, 3 boxes (Box 73)
  - Bill Number Index 1948-1962, 1 boxes (Box 73)
- Post Office Files, 2 linear feet
  Arranged alphabetically by name of city, the Post Office series is a selection of the files maintained by Hoffman documenting the politics behind the selection of postmasters for the numerous post offices within his district. As the selection process was often routine and of like character, this file has been sifted to include the larger cities in each of his six counties and a sampling of the smaller post offices.
  - A-L (Box 74)
  - M-W (Box 75)
- Reference files circa 1939-1962, 5 linear feet
  Reference files consists of card file index plus a series of subject files (much reduced in size). The files are arranged by a numbering sequence devised by the Hoffman office. The files consisted of a scattering of correspondence, articles, clippings, pamphlets, bills, mass mailings from various groups, etc. The files have been reduced to include only material specifically related to Hoffman or to his Congressional and/or political interests.
  - Card indices, 3 boxes (Box 76)
  - Subject Files
    - 1-139 (Box 77)
    - 143-260 (Box 78)
    - 263-375 (Box 79)
    - 377-492 (Box 80)
- Committee files 1947-1962, 8 linear feet
  The Committee Files, 1947-1962, consist of administrative and investigative records from Hoffman's service on the House Committee on Government Operations (formerly called the Committee on Expenditures in Executive Departments). The committee's chief responsibility was to oversee the operation of the executive departments and propose legislative or other methods to control departmental expenditures and increase efficiency. The Committee had broad investigative powers. Hoffman was the senior Republican member of the Committee from 1947 to 1962 and served as chairman in the 80th and 83rd Congresses.
  The files have been arranged by Congress and thereunder by committee and subcommittee. The records include correspondence, minutes, press releases, reports, and topical investigative material. The bulk of the material is from the 83rd Congress, in particular the special Anti-Racketeering Subcommittee. The Anti-Racketeering series is a combined file of three subcommittees on which Hoffman served, a joint subcommittee of the Government Operations and the Labor and Education Committees, a special subcommittee of the Government Operation Committee, chaired by Hoffman, and another subcommittee, chaired by George Bender. These subcommittees conducted a number of investigations on labor union racketeering and corruption, including Teamsters insurance and health and welfare funds, the juke box industry, Washington, D.C. painters union and racketeer-influenced unions in a number of cities.
  Several of the subseries in the Committee files series include photographic exhibits resulting from various labor investigations, primarily of companies on strike. There are also photos illustrating erosion of the Lake Michigan shoreline, 1947-1952, photos of the Hamilton Farm Bureau, Hamilton, Michigan, produce plant and related operation, and photo of the Ford Motor strike of 1941.
  - 80th Congress 1947-1948
    - Committee On Expenditures in Executive Departments (Box 81)
      - Organization and Jurisdiction of Committees (Box 81)
      - Authority of Committees (Box 81)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda (Box 81)
      - Press Releases (Box 81)
      - Summaries of Committee Activity (Box 81)
      - Investigations and Hearings
        - Federal Works Agency - Buchanan, Michigan (Box 81)
        - Full Employment Bill, 4 folders (Box 81)
        - Los Alamos, 5 folders (Box 81)
  - 81st Congress 1949-1950
    - Committee on Expenditures in Executive Departments; Mold on Michigan Raspberry Crop (Hearing Transcript), 3 folders (Box 81)
  - 83rd Congress 1953-1954
    - Government Operations Committee
      - Organization and Procedure of Committee, 2 folders (Box 81)
      - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 81)
      - Press Releases (Box 81)
      - Bills File, 2 folders (Box 81)
      - Investigations and Hearings
        - CIO and Michigan Democratic Party (Box 82)
        - Executive Agency Compliance, 2 folders (Box 82)
        - Internal Revenue Service (Box 82)
        - Military Construction Fraud (Bower case), 2 folders (Box 82)
        - Military Recreation Facilities, Hawaii (includes photos) (Box 82)
        - Military Reorganization Plan, 2 folders (Box 82)
        - Miscellaneous Investigations (Box 82)
        - Office of Rent Stabilization, 3 folders (Box 82)
        - Public Housing, 3 folders (Box 82)
        - Willow Run Bomber Plant, 2 folders (Box 82)
        - Willow Run Bomber Plant, 3 folders (Box 83)
    - Intergovernmental Relation Subcommittee
      - Monthly Reports (Box 83)
      - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 83)
      - Hearings on "Government in business" (Box 83)
    - International Operations Subcommittee
      - Minutes (Box 83)
      - Correspondence (Box 83)
    - Military Operations Subcommittee
      - Minutes and Reports, 2 folders (Box 83)
      - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 83)
      - Defense Research and Development Hearings (Box 83)
    - Public Accounts Subcommittee
      - Correspondence and Reports, 2 folders (Box 83)
      - Investigations (Box 83)
      - Virgin Islands Economy and Government (Box 83)
      - Whirlpool Corporations, LaPorte Aircraft Division (Box 83)
    - Anti-Racketeering Subcommittee
      - Organization and Procedure (Box 83)
      - Correspondence
        - A-L, 3 folders (Box 83)
        - M-Z, 2 folders (Box 84)
      - Press Releases (Box 84)
      - Investigations
        - Baltimore (Box 84)
        - Benton Harbor, Michigan (Box 84)
        - Buffalo, New York (Box 84)
        - Chicago (Box 84)
        - Cleveland, 3 folders (Box 84)
        - Detroit, 8 folders
          - Building Service Employees Union, 2 folders (Box 84)
          - Teamsters, 6 folders (Box 84)
        - Flint (Box 84)
        - Florida (Box 84)
        - Hanford, Washington (Box 84)
        - Indiana (Box 84)
        - Kansas City, 3 folders (Box 84)
        - Los Angeles, 2 folders (Box 84)
        - Minneapolis
          - Teamsters, 10 folders (Box 85)
          - Twin Cities Arsenal (Box 85)
        - New York
          - General (Box 85)
          - International Ladies Garment Workers (Box 85)
          - Meatcutters (Box 85)
        - Ohio (Box 85)
        - Pennsylvania (Box 85)
        - Pontiac, Michigan (Box 85)
        - Southaven, Michigan (Box 85)
        - Toledo, 2 folders (Box 85)
        - Washington, D.C.
          - Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, 8 folders (Box 85)
      - Central States Teamsters Investigation
        - Background Material for Hearings (Box 86)
        - Beck, Dave (Box 86)
        - Dorfman, Allen (Box 86)
        - Dorfman, Paul, 2 folders (Box 86)
        - Fitzsimmons, Frank (Box 86)
        - Hoffa, James R. (Box 86)
        - Central States Employers Association (Box 86)
        - Central States Welfare Fund
          - Minutes, 1950-1953 (Box 86)
          - Insurance, 10 folders (Box 86)
        - Michigan Conference Welfare Fund (Box 86)
      - Juke Box Investigation
        - Akron (Box 87)
        - Chicago (Box 87)
        - Cincinnati (Box 87)
        - Cleveland, 3 folders (Box 87)
        - Detroit (Box 87)
        - Los Angeles (Box 87)
        - Youngstown (Box 87)
        - Presser, William, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - 84th Congress 1955-1956
    - Government Operations Committee